Pretty sure that's Mason.
He says no it isn't.
The code says we're 80% certain.
Still nobody disappointed.
He's behind the drums, keeping perfect time.
Then starts another pointless argument online.
Technically, actually, historically speaking.
Brother, I'm Mason.
Our jar shirt.
Believe in you.
This is good to it. This is good to it because I asked I asked nicely for a cash up
I was gonna send five dollars for a minute
So I have one minute that that fucking big fat cow talking over me
I'll read your text messages now bitch as soon as you hear something from him
Let me know so I can shed his rumor down because ridiculous
It's getting out of hand. That's what you texted me without me. I mean asking you for anything summer come on my channel
My more frequencies
I love you. Hope you're not upset with me over some dumb shit. Everyone else is.
Alexander had already said some very nice things about you.
I'll show you yesterday. Thanks for sticking up for her.
I hope at least you talk to me personally about things just not ghost me. Have a nice day.
I'm not ignoring you. I'm just at work right now. I got a broken well, fractured ankle.
So let me get home and I'll hit you up tonight.
I do understand if you don't come because even Paige is being harassed for supporting me.
I had this best time goofing off and bullshitting last night. Kind of like old times. Thank you.
I needed that. This is me writing to her after I had a good time on a panel with her.
Hope you can make a panel soon. I stream from Psyche's Nightmares.
I'll be on shortly if you're around. Beat is on Sandman's,
Cutie don't listen to these feather feathers fair weather friends. You know, I got your back
Cutie, I I don't like it. It's cutie. I think it was something I don't think I was talking about but I said
I said, I don't know why it put that but whatever lol. Hey, I didn't mean to offend you yesterday
I was really just joking making joking banter. I really don't even drink very much anymore. Anyway, have a good day
Summer there's an emergency. Can we please talk if you have a few minutes to spare soon?
Um, see Alexander Mayer's last lives,
IPG wiki info or IRL news time is really disgusting.
I put the link, please, exclamation point.
Summer, you didn't have five minutes for me?
She rise back.
I didn't, I was whole, I was doing my own shit yesterday.
I'm getting my own, involved with my own,
and I don't want to get involved with Alex shit.
The next day she was in Alexander Mayer's chat,
laughing, laughing with her,
and not saying one word to me.
I said, okay.
I wasn't going to involve you, just ask you something, but get out the popcorn, the show's about to begin.
Well, I was just dealing with all bees yesterday.
What was your question?
You needed it. I said, I'm being doxxed in the worst way.
Severely, obsessively, completely, fraudulently, feeling sad, set up, violated.
I don't know. Probably going to have to disappear. Sorry to bother you.
You know, so now you get it and you know what? She didn't respond but she's on Alexander Mayer's channel
You know some of your bitch, you know what and I try to get one minute to talk and you wouldn't let me talk
Okay, some of your fucking bitch whatever Amber Hall or whatever your fucking name is your fucking bitch. What the hell?
You know, thanks a lot for being there for five minutes.
You have five minutes, you have one minute to listen to me
without your big cow and a man getting involved
and fucking Christine.
Go to fucking hell, bitch and cunt.
I don't care if the police come in and arrest me.
I hate you, Summer, I hate you.
Die, fucking die.
You're not there for me for one minute, not one minute,
not five minutes, fucking die, fucking cunt.
I hate you.